<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AgroVision</string>
    <string name="deskripsi_result">Result description</string>
    <string name="resultDesc">Result description</string>
    <string name="account_settings">Account Settings</string>
    <string name="notification">Push Notification</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="home_page">Welcome to our\nhomepage! Choose\nyour destination...</string>
    <string name="button_result">Back to homepage</string>
    <string name="title_news">Title</string>
    <string name="url">url</string>
    <string name="bookmark">Result</string>
    <string name="desc_result">Description</string>
    <string name="none">Search not found</string>
    <string name="username">Park Sunghoon</string>
    <string name="post_time">1 hour ago</string>
    <string name="image_camera">Image camera</string>
    <string name="camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="home">My Agro</string>
    <string name="Timeline">Timeline</string>
    <string name="setting">Settings\n</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="signup">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="guest">Guest</string>
    <string name="empty_image_warning">Please input the image file first</string>
    <string name="Upload">Analyze</string>
    <string name="fab_login" translatable="false">Login via Floating Action Button</string>
    <string name="fab_signup" translatable="false">Sign Up via Floating Action Button</string>
    <string name="fab_guest" translatable="false">Guest Login via Floating Action Button</string>
    <string name="guest_signup" translatable="false">1</string>
    <string name="guest_login">Guest</string>
    <string name="default_result_description">default result description</string>
    <string name="email">E-mail</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="username_label">Username</string>
    <string name="news">Discover the latest insights.</string>
    <string name="bookmark_label">Your saved analyzes.</string>
    <string name="image_error">Image error</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="result">Detection\'s result</string>
    <string name="permission_camera">Camera permission is needed to use this feature</string>
    <string name="camera_warning">Failed to bind camera provider</string>
    <string name="error_camera">Failed to capture image</string>
    <string name="permission_granted">Permission request granted</string>
    <string name="permission_denied">Permission request denied</string>
    <string name="analyze">Analyze</string>
    <string name="choose_picture">Choose a picture</string>
    <string name="news_appbar">News</string>
    <string name="result_appbar">Result</string>
    <string name="timeline_appbar">Timeline</string>
    <string name="upload_timeline">Upload Timeline</string>
    <string name="detail_bookmark">Bookmark Detail</string>
    <string name="login_success">Login successful!</string>
    <string name="login_error">Failed login, please try again</string>
    <string name="signup_success">Sign up successful!</string>
    <string name="signup_error">Failed sign up! Please try again</string>
    <string name="error">Something went wrong, please try again!</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome Back !</string>
    <string name="login_info">Enter your login details</string>
    <string name="signup_info">Enter your information</string>
    <string name="bookmark_card">Bookmark</string>
    <string name="message_label">Message :</string>
    <string name="hint_upload">What\'s happening?</string>
    <string name="upload_btn">Upload</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="cassava_bacterial_bright">Several disease management techniques have been developed to control the incidence and spread of CBB. Technical cultural practices have been used to reduce pathogen incidence or delay disease effects in the field. Pruning or complete destruction of infected plant tissue, weed removal, use of certified seed, bacterial analysis of stem cuttings and crop rotation are most widely used to limit the presence of the disease in the field. In areas where bacterial wilt disease has not been found, it is important to plant new plants from meristem cultures that are confirmed to be free of the disease. In areas where the disease is already prevalent, care should be taken to ensure that cuttings are taken from healthy plants, and even from highly lignified parts at the base of healthy-looking cassava plants. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="cassava_brown_streak">Management tools are still being explored to control CBSD, and progress has been slow. Development of cassava resistant to CMD and CBSD is urgently needed. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="cassava_green_mottle">There are currently no pesticides or antibiotics that can be used to treat CGM. The most effective way to prevent the spread of the disease is to control the whiteflies that spread it. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="cassava_healthy">Keep it up! Your cassava plants seem to be healthy. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="cassava_mosaic">Prevention methods for the spread of CMV include, avoiding planting alternative hosts of the virus, such as castor beans (Ricinus communis), adjacent to cassava, avoiding planting cassava if a neighboring field has cassava infected with the virus as it can be carried by whitefly. Prevention methods also include not planting alternative hosts of the whitefly virus vector, such as tomatoes. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="corn_blight">Management of NCLB can be done mainly by using hybrids that have resistance, but since resistance may not be perfect or may fail, it is better to use an integrated approach with different cropping practices and fungicides. Staking out fields and monitoring local conditions are essential to control this disease. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="corn_gray_leaf_spot">The most appropriate and economical method to reduce yield loss due to corn leaf spot is to introduce resistant varieties of plants. In places where leaf spot occurs, these plants can eventually grow and remain resistant to the disease. Although the disease cannot be eliminated and resistant varieties show disease symptoms, by the end of the growing season, the disease is not so effective in reducing yield. SC 407 has proven to be a common maize variety resistant to gray leaf spot disease. If gray leaf spot infection is high, this variety may require fungicide applications to reach full potential. Susceptible varieties should not be planted in previously infected areas. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="corn_healthy">Keep it up! Your corn crop seems healthy. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="corn_rust">Rust disease is very difficult to treat. Fungicides, such as Mancozeb, can help but cannot eradicate the disease. Some organic preventive solutions are available and sulphur powder is known to stop spore germination. High standards of hygiene, good soil drainage and careful watering can minimize the problem. Any appearance of rust should be dealt with immediately by removing and burning all affected leaves. Composting, or leaving infected vegetation on the ground will spread the disease. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="rice_bacterial_blight">Management of bacterial leaf blight is most often done by planting rice plants that are resistant to the disease. PSB Rc82 is the standard rice variety used in Southeast Asia, and the use of this cultivar allows the harvest of approximately 0.8 million metric tons of rice per growing season that would otherwise be lost to bacterial leaf blight. Macassane, a new variety released in 2011, has been shown to have better resistance to bacterial leaf blight and is currently used in Mozambique. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="rice_brown_spot">Fungal spread can be prevented by using certified disease-free seed and using available resistant varieties such as MAC 18. Avoiding tight seed sowing can also help prevent fungal spread as it reduces moisture. Maintaining weed control and removing volunteer plants in the field can also prevent the spread of the fungus, as well as burning the stumps of infected plants. Seed treatment can also be used as a preventive measure. Seeds can be treated with fungicides or alternatively by soaking the seeds in cold water for 8 hours before treating with hot water (53 to 54°C) for 10 to 12 minutes before planting. Soil treatment can also be used to prevent the spread of C. miyabeanus. Addition of potassium and calcium if the soil is deficient can help improve disease resistance. However, excessive use of nitrogen fertilizers should be avoided. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="rice_healthy">Keep it up! Your rice crop seems to be healthy. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="rice_leaf_blast">To effectively control M. grisea infection, an integrated management program should be implemented to avoid overuse of a single control method and counter genetic resistance. For example, removing crop residues can reduce the occurrence of overwintering and prevent inoculation the following season. Another strategy is to plant resistant rice varieties that are not easily infected by M. grisea. Knowledge of the pathogenicity of M. grisea and its need for air moisture suggests other control strategies such as regulated irrigation and combinations of chemical treatments with different modes of action. Managing the amount of water supplied to the crop limits spore mobility and thus reduces the chance of infection. Chemical controls such as Carpropamid have been shown to prevent the penetration of appressoria into the epidermal cells of rice, leaving the grains unaffected. Papajani et al. 2015 found that essential oils from Origanum vulgare and Rosmarinus officinalis were effective in vitro, and provided a threshold treatment. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="rice_tungro">Exact planting time is a source of tungro virus inoculum. In order to avoid infection with viruses originating from cattails, the seedbed is planted at least 5 (five) days after tillage is complete and cattails are no longer present. Planting is attempted as early as possible so that when the green leafhopper population reaches its peak, the rice plants are already > 60 hst and more resistant to tungro. The right planting time can be determined by considering fluctuations in the green leafhopper population and the presence of annual tungro. The right planting time is the planting time that can avoid plants during the vulnerable phase (≤ 30 hst) does not coincide with high tungro pressure (green leafhopper population and the presence of high tungro symptoms). Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="sugarcane_healthy">Keep it up! Your sugarcane crop seems to be healthy. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="sugarcane_mosaic">The disease is spread through sap containing the virus and can move to other areas mostly by mechanical means such as lawn mowers and other equipment. To minimize the spread of sugarcane mosaic virus, all equipment used should be sterilized. Fungicides and other pesticides have proven ineffective in managing viral diseases. The best way to manage viral diseases is through host plant resistance. The main management tool is to transform virus genes into maize plants, but transgenic crops are increasingly raising concerns over their potential negative ecological effects, such as reversal of silencing by virus suppressors, complementation, synergy and gene flow among closely related organisms. Resistant strains have been used to control the virus in the southern United States and the tropics; however, these strains have not been able to adapt to colder conditions such as those in central and northwestern Europe. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="sugarcane_red_rot">The development of red rot can be stopped or slowed down by the treatment of an aluminum alkoxide solution, which increases the pH value and becomes (in the presence of water) a buffer for inorganic aluminum salts on the skin. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="sugarcane_rust">Currently scientists at the Agricultural Research Service are genetically analyzing the fungus that causes citrus rust to help combat this problem. Source: Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="sugarcane_yellow">Mycovellosiella koepkei is a fungal plant pathogen that infects sugarcane. Source: Wikipedia</string>

</resources>